<Document>
  # FLUXIA-CLASS CHEMISTRY SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ChemMaster"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ChemDispenser"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineChemicals"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PosterLegitPeriodicTable"/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-4

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Uranium

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A small-to-medium, chemistry-focused shuttle for 2 chemists, with their laboratories, and a garden with botanical supplies."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the main APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).

  ## 1.2. S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorSuperPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FuelUranium"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the generator unit is properly anchored.
  - Check that the generator unit is connected to the cable terminal of your SMES via HV.
  - Check the fuel remaining in the generator unit.
  - Set the generator unit output power to 22 kW.
  - Enable Injection.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Ensure that an air canister is connected to the connector port.
  - Check that the air canister is of a suitable atmos mixture (~21% oxygen, ~79% nitrogen).
  - Enable the gas pump into the distribution system.

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Fluxia-class chemistry shuttles are equipped with one APC unit that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. An unmodified Fluxia-class ship requires ~25.7 kW of power to remain operational.

  # SHUTTLE DETAILS

  ## 1. Overall

  The shuttle has integral pressure, fire, air, resistance; being [color=red]equipped with fire doors, alarms, and safety equipment[/color], but also shutters in case of manipulating hazardous chemicals. This shuttle was built by Dark Matter Enterprises, with the word safety in front of everything.

  ## 2. Top of the shuttle

  ## 2.1. Cockpit
  
  Armed with a [color=#334E6D]fax machine[/color], [color=#334E6D]the shuttle console[/color], [color=#334E6D] the station records[/color], paper, a pen and even a cell recharger, this cockpit is not to be mixed up with an office cubicle. A [color=#334E6D]holopad[/color] as well as two racks and a chair are present too.

  ## 2.2. Power Closet

  Powered with two S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N.-type portable generators, a substation but also a SMES unit, in order to achieve a maximum delay between power outage, this shuttle is eco-friendly with its uranium-fueled power.

  ## 2.3. Safety Closet

  This closet is the home to your air distribution, but also houses crude cleaning equipement. It also has a fire closet and a radiation suit closet for any hazardous chemical incidents.

  ## 2.4. Hall

  In the hall of the shuttle, you can find your emergency equipments: fire extinguisher, defibrillator, APC, but also a water cooler so you can hydrate in an emergency!

  ## 3. Chemistry Labs

  Two opposed chemistry labs, entirely independant on their own, for those extremely focus crews. They are both equipped with a ChemMaster, a filled ChemDispenser, hotplate, grinder, electrolysis, a filled locker, a sink and a drain. It is also equipped with paper and a chair, as well as the periodic table just to be safe.

  ## 4. Garden

  Equipped with seven trays, this garden allows any hydroponic dream you might have. This garden is also supplied with 3 buckets, a water tank, a NutriMax vendor, HyDrobe vendor, a MegaSeed Servitor, a seed extractor, a filled locker of botanist supplies, and a grinder alongside a beaker.

  ## 5. Dock

  In the dock, you will find, two EVA suits, two emergency internal closets, and two spots reserved for crates/canisters.

</Document>
